

# **Profile**

Based in Brazil, lived in Arlington, TX for 4 years 2007-2011, started into programming in 2016, with web developing, participated in the Brazilian Computer Olympics studying back-end PHP/MySQL and some Coldfusion. Transitioned to Python with Flask late 2017. Entered CS50 in 2019 learn t C, data structures, algorithms and pointers.

# **Employment History**

# HTML/CSS, IZOTX Brazil, online

FEBRUARY 2017 - APRIL 2017

First job staying only few months due to company being closed down in Brazil.

## CNC Programmer, Pimentel Ferramentas, Bragança Paulista

AUGUST 2012 - PRESENT

Programming in g-code to increase tool production.

Building management system with flask framework and ORM library.

Building e commerce in WordPress for selling tools.

# **Portfolio**

# Wordpress - E-commerce, Bragança Paulista

JUNE 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

Built an epoxy selling site with wordpress using woocommerce, elementor, social plugins.

www.epoxibraganca.com.br

# Startup Site - B2MO, Bragança Paulista

OCTOBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

Built a simple site with PHPMailer, OOP, JS, for a startup promoting their work on sustainable energy.

b2motech.com.br

### ONU - European Cultural Heritage, Bragança Paulista

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Built a WordPress for a European Cultural Heritage school's fair with each group posting an European country.

No longer hosted due to financial reasons. So It's freely opened at GitHub.

#### Covid-19- Project, Bragança Paulista

JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

I've built an Coronavirus project with a group:

Debugging and coding in JavaScript, helping with HTML/CSS and deploying to Heroku.

# Courses

# **Details**

Avenida José Gomes da Rocha Leal , Bragança Paulista, 12900-300, Brazil 55 11 92002 3609 <u>lauropimentel12@gmail.com</u>

NATIONALITY

Brazilian

DATE OF BIRTH

07/16/2002

# Links

Linkedin

<u>Instagram</u>

# **Skills**

Web Programming Skills

JavaScript ES6

React.js / React native

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap , JavaScript

SQL

PHP OOP

Flask Framework

Wordpress

C/C++

# Languages

Portuguese

English

### CS50x, Harvard University

JULY 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

### CS50W, Harvard University (edx)

SEPTEMBER 2020 - APRIL 2021

# Full Stack Flask Developer, Pirple.com

OCTOBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

#### PHP Course, Sololearn

JANUARY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

## PHP CRUD, Udemy

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2017

### Swift, Sololearn

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2020

#### JavaScript, Sololearn

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

#### **Databases and PHP, Team Treehouse**

JANUARY 2017 - JULY 2017

### HTML/CSS, CodeAcademy

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

# Swift, Sololearn

JUNE 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

# **Education**

# Senior High School, Educare, Bragança Paulista

FEBRUARY 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

Finishing High School

# 9th Grade, Colégio Objetivo, Bragança Paulista

JULY 2013 - DECEMBER 2017

### 3rd & 4th grade, Escola Muncipal Tibiriça, Bragança Paulista

FEBRUARY 2011 - DECEMBER 2012

# 3rd Grade, Beth Anderson Elementary School, Arlington, TX

JULY 2007 - DECEMBER 2010

# Extra-curricular activities

# CNC Programmer, Pimentel Ferramentas, Bragança Paulista

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

# iPhone Repair, Self-employed

JULY 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

Started an iPhone repair business fixing both hardware and software .